天啊  你真美
God, you're beautiful.
我们为什么要抗拒这种感觉呢
Why are we fighting this?
你跟我一样都想要的
You know you want it to happen as much as l do.
我想要你  我需要你
l want you. l need you.
让我跟你做爱
Let me make love to you.
我不想要介入这场真爱还是什么的
l don't wanna stand in the way of true love or anything...
但是我想如果你找一个甜瓜来爱
...but l think a cantaloupe
可能会比较不痛
might hurt less.
不是啦  我是在练习我的台词
No, l'm rehearsing my lines.
他们在《我们的日子》里头帮我
They're giving me a romantic story
安插了爱情故事情节
on Days of Our Lives.
这是我的角色第一次恋爱
lt's the first time my character's gotten one.
我很紧张  我想要把他演好
l'm nervous. l want it to be good.
自从你上次做那个狗食广告之后
l haven't seen you this worked-up
我就没有看你这么认真练习过
since you did that dog-food commercial...
而且那次你还以为是要跟
...and you thought you were gonna be
一只真的会说话的狗一起演出
with a real talking dog.
是啊  那次我真的很失望
Yeah, that was a disappointment.
你想过来片厂看我表现如何吗
You wanna come down to the set and tell me if l'm doing okay?
-真的吗  -是啊
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
只要你保证不要再被赶出去
You just have to promise not to get thrown out again.
-那只是个无心之错  -没错
- That was an honest mistake. - Right.
"天啊  这是男厕所吗   我真是好蠢"
''Oh, my God. ls this the men's room? l feel so foolish.
"你一直都很清楚自己要当演员吗"
Have you always known you wanted to be an actor?''
是啊  真是精采的一天
Yeah, that was an awesome day.
《老友记》  第九季 第19集  瑞秋的梦
Friends S09E19 The One With Rachel's Dream
-嘿  -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你们接下来几个星期
So do you guys wanna come eat dinner
有想要到我们餐厅用餐吗
at the restaurant sometime in the next few weeks?
-好啊  -我很想
- Sure. - l'd love to.
喔  可能没办法
Well, you can't.
我们下个月全部都被订满了
We're booked solid for the next month.
喔  我不能帮你按摩
Well, l can't give you a massage...
因为我的执照又被取消了
...because my license has been revoked again.
菲比  发生什么事
Phoebe, what happened?
喔  只是个意外
Well, it was an accident, you know.
当用很多精油的时候
lt's a lot of oil
有时候手是会滑的
and sometimes the hand just slips.
我要给你个惊喜
Have l got a surprise for you.
回家去打包吧
Pack your bags.
喔  不
Oh, no.
你们七年之内不可以离婚的
You guys aren't supposed to get divorced for seven years.
什么  不  我是要带莫妮卡
What? No, l'm taking Monica
去佛蒙特州的浪漫客栈度假
to a romantic inn in Vermont.
还好  好的
Oh, good.
很好  试着找回往日情怀
Okay, good for you. Trying to recapture the magic.
怎么样  你可以请假吗
So what do you say? Can you get out of work?
亲爱的  我没有办法
Honey, l can't.
餐厅现在忙疯了
Things are crazy at the restaurant.
你真的那么忙吗
You're really that busy?
是的  我很抱歉  我真的很忙
Yeah. l'm sorry, l really am.
没关系  我来试着更改日期好了
That's okay. l'll just try and reschedule.
嗨  我是钱德勒·宾
Hi, this is Chandler Bing.
我在你们这预定过
l made a reservation there...
现在我需要更改日期
...and l need to change it.
无法退费是什么意思
What do you mean, it's nonrefundable?
我不能择期再去吗
Well, can l just come some other time?
你不能破例吗
Can't you make an exception?
告诉他们我是
Tell them l'm a chef
纽约一家大餐厅的主厨
at a big New York restaurant.
告诉他们在两星期以后
Tell them that in two weeks,
我又会再度成为很棒的按摩师
l will once again be a masseuse in good standing.
听着  这实在太可笑了
Look, this is ridiculous.
这钱我不会付的  好吧
l'm not paying for that room, okay?
好的  非常谢谢你
Well, thank you very much.
我得去佛蒙特州
Yeah, l'm going to Vermont.
别担心  你可以用你的旅游保险
Don't worry, use your travel insurance.
我没有旅游保险
l don't have travel insurance.
当人们活在危机边缘的时候
Well, this is what happens
就是会发生这种事
when people live on the edge.
你何不跟罗斯一起去呢
Why don't you take Ross?
你不觉得那会有点奇怪吗
Don't you think that'll be a little weird?
两个大男人住一间浪漫客栈
l mean, two guys in a romantic inn?
不会啊  如果有两张床就好了
No, not if the room has two beds.
就算是吧
l guess.
但是还是有点… "月光船游"
lt still seems a little-- ''Moonlight boat ride''?!
乔伊
Joey,
这是奥莉维亚献出第一夜的那张床吗
is this the bed where Olivia lost her virginity?
我不知道  倒是有个临时演员献出过
l don't know, but one of the extras sure did.
瑞秋
Listen, Rach.
再次谢谢你过来看我的演出
Thanks again for coming down to watch my scenes.
拜托  亲爱的
Please, honey.
我光是想到你要我的支持  我就...
Just the fact that you want me here to support you, l'm--
喔  天啊  那是克利斯·桑德斯吗
Oh, my God. ls that Christian Saunders?
他真的是非常帅
He is so gorgeous!
而且也非常"同志"
And also, so gay.
在我脑海中
Well, in my head,
他做了很多不是"同志"的事
he's done some pretty not-gay stuff.
在圣诞晚会上
Well, at the Christmas party,
他跟圣诞老公公
him and Santa
做了很多绝对是"同志"的事
did some definitely-gay stuff.
乔伊  乔伊  我们准备好要拍你了
Joey? Joey, we're ready for you.
好的  祝我好运
Okay. All right, wish me luck.
你不是真的需要运气才做的好
Okay. Not that you need it,
但… 天啊  那是杰斯·莱西特吗
but good-- God! ls that Chase Lassiter?
他是异性恋  对吧
He's straight, right?
瑞秋  如果没有你在这里猜测…
Rach, I got to say, if you weren't here wondering...
这些男的是不是"同志"…
...if these guys were gay,
我还真的不知道我能不能演得好
l don't know if l could do this.
我很抱歉  你说的对
l'm sorry, you're right.
很抱歉  祝你好运
l'm sorry. Good luck.
拜托准备好  安静
On a bell, please. Quietly.
开拍
And action!
德雷克  你来这里做什么呢
Drake, what are you doing here?
阻止你嫁给不对的人…
Stopping you from marrying the wrong man...
犯下你这辈子最大的错误
...and making the biggest mistake of your life.
出去
Get out.
你并不爱他
You don't love him.
你知道什么是爱吗
What do you know about love?
我知道那晚我们在
l know what l felt that night
桥下接吻的感觉是什么
when we kissed under the bridge.
那个吻并没有发生
That kiss never happened.
那么  这个呢
Well, what about this one?
我说过了  滚出去
Now, l told you to get out.
好  我走
Fine, l'll go.
但是让我问你一个问题
But let me ask you one question.
你看起来很面熟  我们有...
You look real familiar. Have we--?
嘘  他要问她问题
Shh! He's asking her a question.
你可以渡过一生而不知道
Can you live the rest of your life
我们如果在一起会是如何吗
never knowing what we could have been?
我没有选择
l don't have a choice.
你有选择的
Yes, you do.
你有的
我才是那个没有选择的人
l'm the one who doesn't have a choice
因为我...
because l....
因为我无法停止爱你
Because l can't stop loving you.
别那样说
Don't say that.
你叫我停下来吧
Tell me to stop.
你只要...
Just...
叫我停下来
...tell me to stop.
-卡  -不
- Cut! - No!
卡也好  你说了算
Or, cut. You know, that's your call.
每道菜都很美味
Everything was delicious.
谢谢你
Thank you.
真的  尤其是鸭肉更是美味绝伦
lt was. The duck in particular was superb.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你还没有开口说话
You haven't said anything.
其实我有一个小小的抱怨
Actually, l do have one small complaint.
喔  请说  我欢迎各种批评指教
Well, please, l welcome criticism.
餐厅外面的歌手
The musician right outside the restaurant
有点破坏气氛
is kind of a mood killer.
什么歌手
What musician?
有个国家叫阿根廷
And there's a country called Argentinaaaa,
这地方我从来没去过
it's a place I've never seeeeen.
但是有人告诉我  那五十比索就能买一个人的脾
But I'm told for fifty pesos you can buy a human spleen.
人的...脾  欧嘞
Humaaan spleeeeen. Ol?
你在这里做什么呢
What are you doing here?
你说你们的客人都排队排到街上
You said you had customers lined up in the street,
所以我就过来娱乐他们了
so l'm here to entertain.
很好
Great.
是啊  一切都进行的很好
Yeah, it really has been great too.
他们一定有看我表演过
They must have seen me play before...
因为他们一直要点我的许多歌曲
...because they requested a bunch of my songs.
像是《你逊毙了》
Yeah, ''You Suck'' ...
还有《闭嘴回家去》
...and ''Shut Up and Go Home.''
听着  菲比
Listen, Phoebe.
你知道我很爱听你的歌的
You know how much l love listening to your music...
但是…
...but....
但是什么
But what?
这是个蛮高级的场所
This is kind of a classy place.
好的  不用多说了
Okay, say no more.
那女人不光长得胖
It wasn't just that she was fat
她身上也是垃圾味儿
the woman smelled like garbage!
大家一起来
Everyone!
那女人不光长得胖
It wasn't just that she was fat,
她身上也是垃圾味儿
the woman smelled like garbaaaaaage!
高级  不是吗
Classy, huh?
嗨  我是 钱德勒·宾
Hi, Chandler Bing.
我有订房
l have a reservation.
欢迎来到栗子客栈
Welcome to the Chestnut lnn.
你们是从哪里来的呢
Where are you joining us from?
纽约
New York.
"大苹果"
The Big Apple.
抱歉  他太兴奋了
I'm sorry, he's a little wound up.
我们来这里的路上 每间枫糖糖果店都有停下来
We had to stop at every maple-candy stand on the way here.
我吃光了要买给大家的礼物
l ate all my gifts for everybody.
我很抱歉  电脑没有登记您的预定
l'm sorry, there's no record of your reservation in the computer.
那是不可能的  请再查一次
That's impossible.Can you check again, please.
请再查一次
Check again, please.
我很抱歉  没有
l'm sorry, it's not here.
没有
lt's not there.
让我搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
我有打过电话来
l called to try to
试着要取消我的预约
cancel my reservation...
你们告诉我不能取消
...was told it's not refundable.
然后我们开了六小时的车到这里
Then we drove six hours all the way up here...
现在你又说我们没有订房
...and now we don't have a reservation?
我不知道该说什么
l don't know what to say.
她不知道该说什么
She doesn't know what to say.
那给我们最便宜的房间就好了
Just give us the cheapest room you have.
我们现在剩下来的房间就只有精致套房
The only thing we have available is our deluxe suite.
价格是每晚六百元
The rate is $600.
这真的过分
That's insane.
真是太过分了
lt's totally insane.
我们开车回家吧
Dude, let's drive home.
可以在回家路上的
We'll hit all the maple-candy stores
再去每间枫糖糖果店
on the way back...
而且如果他们关门了
...and if they're closed,
或许我们可以找棵树
then maybe we'll tap a tree
自己做枫糖
and make some ourselves.
那个房间有个衣橱
Does that room have a closet
可以让我把他锁起来吗
l can lock him in?
我们要那间房
We'll take it.
太好了
Great.
他们完全就是在抢劫我们
They are totally ripping us off!
老兄  别担心
Dude, don't worry about it.
我知道要如何让你花的钱回本
l know how to make your money back.
这是间不错的饭店
This is a nice hotel.
有很多福利设施
Plenty of amenities.
我们只要尽量拿走那些东西就好了
We just load up on those.
像是这些苹果  不要只拿一个
Like those apples. lnstead of taking one...
我给他拿六个
...l take six.
太棒了  一个苹果一百块  我们已经赚回来了
Great. At $ 100 an apple, we're there.
别这样  你知道我的意思的
Come on, you get the idea.
我们很快就可以回本了
You know, we'll make our money back in no time.
老兄  你在发抖耶
Dude, you're shaking.
是糖在搞怪
lt's the sugar.
可以帮我拿苹果吗
Could you hold the apple?
-嗨  -嘿
- Hi. - Hey.
乔伊  我要跟你说
Joey, l gotta tell you,
我整天都在想你的演出
l have been thinking all day about that scene you did.
你真是棒透了
l mean, you were amazing.
你知道的  编剧很棒
You know, the writing was good.
导演也很棒
And the director's good.
我的对戏演员也很棒
And my costar's good.
但是他们还是不如我棒
But they're not as good as me!
你得告诉我明天会发生什么事
You have to tell me what happens tomorrow.
我现在正在看剧本
l'm going over the script now.
你要帮我一起对台词吗
Wanna read lines with me?
我吗  喔  我不是演员的料
Me? Oh, l'm not an actress.
好吧  那我去找莫妮卡
All right, l can ask Monica.
去她的  那角色是我的
Screw her! That part is mine!
好的  从这一页开头开始
Okay, so just from the top of the page right here.
好的
Okay.
你好  德雷克  在这见到你我很惊讶
Hello, Drake. l'm surprised to see you here.
我不敢相信你嫁给他了
l can't believe you married him.
我能有什么选择呢
Well, what choice did l have?
他把我妹妹关在地牢里
He was keeping my sister in a dungeon.
那我们呢
So, what about us?
我们对彼此的感觉呢
Everything we feel for each other?
结束了  你必须要接受
lt's over. You have to accept that.
当我知道我再也无法把你拥入怀中
How can l, knowing l'll never hold you
或是碰触你的肌夫
in my arms again...
或是感觉你的双唇 或是永远无法跟你做爱
...or touch your skin or feel your lips...
我怎么能够做的到呢
...knowing l'll never make love to you?
我怎么能接受
How can l accept
我再也无法亲吻你
that l can never kiss you again...
而我现在最想要做的
...when it's all l can do
就只是亲吻你
not to kiss you right now?
亲我
Kiss me.
什么
What?
亲我
Kiss me.
瑞秋  剧本不是那样写的
Rach, it doesn't say that.
不  是我说的
No, l'm saying it.
但是…
But--
不要说话
Just don't talk.
这剧情够新
Well, that's new.
嗨  我是206号套房的罗斯·盖勒
Hi, this is Ross Geller in suite 206.
我忘了带几样东西
I think l've forgotten a couple of things.
你可以帮我送几样赠送的
Could you have some complimentary toiletries
卫生用品到我房间里来吗
sent up to my room?
谢谢你 好的  牙刷  牙膏
Thank you. Okay, a toothbrush, toothpaste...
刮胡刀  漱口水  体香剂
...razor, mouthwash, deodorant,
牙线  绷带  刮胡乳液  收敛水
floss, Band-Aids, shaving cream, after-shave.
我觉得我好像漏了什么东西
And l feel like l'm forgetting something.
你还有什么东西是我没有提到的呢
ls there anything else you have that l haven't asked for already?
好  那就送一些卫生棉条上来
Yeah, go ahead, send up some tampons.
你拿了什么
What'd you get?
《美国时报》
USA Today.
很好  跟其它的放在一起
Nice. Put it with the others.
而且我还多拿了两个苹果
And l also got two more apples.
还差四个就可以做水果花篮了
We're four short of a bushel!
天啊  我觉得充满活力
God, l feel so alive.
我喜欢乡间生活
l love being in the country!
还有  我从餐厅里拿了这些…
Also, got these great salt and pepper shakers...
盐巴胡椒罐
...from the restaurant.
这不好
That's not cool.
兄弟  这一切都不好
Dude, none of this is cool.
听着  钱德勒  你要找出介于偷窃...
Look, Chandler, you have to find the line between stealing...
拿取饭店欠你的东西之间的界线
...and taking what the hotel owes you.
例如  吹风机  不不不
For example: A hair dryer, no, no.
但是洗发精跟润发乳  可以可以
But shampoos and conditioners, yes, yes.
盐巴罐就过分了
Now, the salt shaker is off limits.
但是盐巴…
But the salt....
我希望我刚刚有想清楚点
l wish l'd thought this through.
我想我知道你的意思了
l think l get what you mean, though.
就像台灯是饭店的…
Like, the lamp is the hotel's...
但是灯泡… 喔  你已经拿了
...but the bulbs-- Oh, you already got that.
我的朋友  这可不是我第一次住饭店
Not my first time in a hotel, my friend.
好的  那这个呢
Okay, how about this?
不不不
No, no, no.
你不能拿遥控器
You can't take the remote control.
是的  但是可以拿电池
Yes, but the batteries.
谢谢  太谢谢你了
Thank you. Thank you very much.
我们来吃枫糖庆祝吧
Let's celebrate with some maple candy.
不
No!
至少告诉我你把它藏哪里去了
At least tell me where you hid it.
-我可以问你一个问题吗  -好的
- Can l ask you a question? - Yeah.
你有没有做过任何…
Have you ever had any...
奇异的...浪漫的梦呢
...weird, romantic dreams?
让我想想
Let me think.
我年轻的时候
When l was younger,
我曾经梦过跟麦当劳的卡通市长结婚（Mayor McCheese:以前一个麦当劳的卡通人物  头是一个汉堡）
l used to dream that l got married to Mayor McCheese.
然后在我们新婚之夜  我吃了他的头
And on our wedding night, l ate his head.
好的
Okay.
这一点也…
Well, this is like that...
不像是那样
...in no way.
我昨晚梦到我想要亲乔伊
l had a dream last night that l wanted to kiss Joey.
哇  你是说真的亲吻他吗
Wow! You mean like ''kiss him'' kiss him?
是啊  我是说那种很激情的
Oh, yeah. l mean, it was pretty intense.
-为什么会那样呢  -我不知道
- What brought that on? - l don't know.
或许跟我看到他演出那场爱情戏有关
Maybe it had to do with the fact l saw him do a love scene.
-爱情戏  跟谁呢  -奥莉维亚
- A love scene? With who? - Olivia.
奥莉维亚
Olivia?!
我以为她要跟康纳结婚了
l thought she was marrying Connor?!
对了  现实生活比较重要
Oh, right. Real life more important.
你认为我的梦代表什么吗
You think my dream means anything?
我不知道
l don't know.
你看到他演出爱情戏
l mean, you saw him do a love scene.
或许对乔伊没有感觉
So maybe you don't have a thing for Joey.
或许你是对德雷克有感觉
Maybe you have a thing for Drake.
是啊  在梦里是当乔伊
Well, it was Joey reading
在念德雷克台词的时候
Drake's lines in the dream.
当然啰  相信我
Of course it was. Trust me,
只要是跟心理学有关
when it comes to psychology...
我是很内行的
...l know what l'm talking about.
我在大学的时候修过两堂心理学
l took two psych classes in college.
你一堂课修了两次
You took the same class twice.
那很难耶
lt was hard!
我知道
l know.
嘿
Hey.
嗨  菲比
Hi, Phoebe.
莫妮卡
Here, Monica,
瞧瞧我为了要到你餐厅演唱
look what l got to wear
买了什么
when l play at your restaurant.
等等
Wait.
我想这会提高
Right? l think this might even class up
《没有割包皮男人之民谣》的格调
''The Ballad of the Uncircumcised Man.''
菲比…
Phoebe...
或许我之前说的不够清楚
...maybe l wasn't clear before.
我真的很喜欢在这里听你的音乐
l really love listening to your music here.
但是我的餐厅是比较高级的地方
But my restaurant, it's sort of an upscale place.
好的  好吧
Right, yeah, okay.
我会要管家帮我把
l'll ask the butler to fetch
我的钻石从保险箱拿出来
my diamonds out of the vault.
菲比  不是你穿的衣服的关系
Phoebe, it's not what you wear.
是你的歌
lt's sort of your songs.
我只是觉得你不应该再到餐厅演唱了
l just don't think you should play at the restaurant anymore.
好的  没关系  我就…
Okay. Fine, l'll just--
我把帽子拿回去退
l'll take the hat back.
好了
There.
嘿  我办公室发生一件最好笑...
Hey, so, you guys, the funniest thing happened at work the--
我的歌不够格登上你们餐厅的大雅之堂吗
My songs aren't good enough for your restaurant?
好吧  我们还在谈那个
Okay, we're still on that.
我没有说它们不够格
l didn't say they weren't good enough.
那有什么不对呢
Then what's wrong with them?
是怎样  他们不够格配你的
What, they don't go with your
一丁点份的自负的食物吗
tiny portions of pretentious food?
-一丁点份  -是啊不好意思…
- Tiny portions? - Yeah, well, ''Excuse me.
我点了熏鲑鱼开胃菜
l ordered the smoked salmon appetizer,
但是我看不到鲑鱼  我看不到
but l can't see it. l can't see it.''
菲比  份量不是最重要的
Phoebe, it's not about quantity.
喔  品质也不是最重要的
Well, it's not about quality.
真的吗  你想要谈品质吗
Oh, really? You wanna talk about quality?
你有听过什么叫"调"吗
Have you ever heard of a ''key''?
那是大家唱歌要对的
lt's what some people sing in.
至少我所有的歌都没有大蒜味
Well, at least all my songs don't taste like garlic.
是的  莫妮卡 还有其它的东西可以拿来调味的
Yeah, there are other ingredients, Monica.
所以我们要这样做啰
So that's what we're doing.
当我在咖啡厅里跟着你的歌打拍子时
When l'm in a coffeehouse bopping along to one of your songs...
我是有戴耳塞的
...l'm wearing earplugs.
是耳塞还是蒜头塞呢
Earplugs or cloves of garlic?
你知道吗  我收回我所说的话
You know what? l take back what l said before.
继续到餐厅演唱吧
Keep playing at the restaurant,
因为你的音乐会把人逼进餐厅里...
because with your music driving people inside...
我们吧台的营业量会疯狂激长的
...my bar sales have gone up like crazy.
他们都点什么呢  蒜头马提尼吗
What are people having, the garlic martini?
这是您的帐单
Here's your bill.
希望您还住的愉快
We hope you enjoyed your stay.
喔  我们很愉快
Oh, we did.
而且你们的台灯都还在
And you still have all your lamps.
我没有算进税金
l didn't factor in the room tax.
兄弟  不用担心
Dude, don't worry about it.
我找到了一台没人看管的女佣拖车
l found an unattended maid's cart.
我们是居领先地位的
We're way ahead of the game.
-喔  我的天 -怎样
-Oh, my God. -What?
那盆子里有新的东西
There's something new in the bowl.
听着  我们拿够了  走吧
Look, we have enough. Just walk away.
不  但是我想要松果
No, but l want the pine cones.
外面就有一片森林
There's a forest right outside.
那不一样
lt's not the same.
好吧  快点
Okay, go quick.
谢谢你们令人愉快的服务
Thank you for a delightful stay.
我的枫糖糖果
My maple candy!
吃了"家福"的餐  包你上西天
Food here at 'Javu'.. will kill you..
the food here at 'Javu' ... will kill you..
原来是你  我还以为有人
lt's just you. l thought someone
拿了一袋子的猫往墙上挥
was swinging a bag of cats against the wall.
你最好回去厨房
You'd better get back in that kitchen.
蒜头是不会自己多用自己的
The garlic's not gonna overuse itself.
好了  你现在必须要停唱了
Okay, you have to stop playing now.
为什么
Why?
我的歌干扰到的人只有你
The only person my playing is bothering is you.
是吗  我们来解决这件事  来吧
Oh, yeah? Let's settle this. Come on.
把你的蒜头手拿开
Get your garlic peelers off me.
不好意思  不好意思
Excuse me? Excuse me?
我是莫妮卡·盖勒  这里的主厨
Hi, l'm Monica Geller. l'm the head chef here.
好的  我本来真的希望有人鼓掌的
Okay, l was actually expecting a little applause there,
但是没关系
but whatever.
一个问题  请大家举手回答
Quick question. By a show of hands...
你们有谁被这女人
...how many of you were bothered
在外面唱歌干扰到呢
by this woman's singing outside?
好的  好的
Okay, okay.
你们有谁喜欢外面的音乐呢
How many of you enjoyed the music outside?
让我问你们这个问题
Let me ask you this question.
有谁认为音乐还好...
How many thought the music was fine...
但是跟本餐厅的格调不符呢
...but not in keeping with the tone of the restaurant?
好的  谁认为这个餐厅的格调是
Okay, well, who identified this restaurant's tone as
"自以为是又充满蒜头味"呢
''pretentious-comma-garlicky''?
好的  有谁觉得食物是很美味的
Okay, who thinks the food is delicious
而一点点做作是没关系的
and a little pretension never hurt anyone?
好了  没关系
Okay, well, all right,
有谁觉得食物很好 音乐也很棒
who thinks the food is fine, the music was fine...
但是你的晚餐已经
...but your evening was ruined
被这个持续不断的民意调查给毁了
by this incessant poll-taking?
不好意思
Excuse us.
好了  我问你
All right, here's a question.
有谁认为她的餐厅是那么的高级…
Who was so worried about her restaurant being fancy...
让她过分的担心
...that she made a big deal
她的朋友会演唱不适当的音乐…
about her friend playing her music...
而现在真的觉得很难过呢
...and feels really bad about it now?
有谁很愚蠢又很顽固...
Well, who was so stupid and stubborn...
批评了她朋友的烹饪技术…
...that she lashed out against her friend's cooking...
而其实她是觉得她的烹饪很好呢
...which she actually thinks is pretty great?
我很抱歉
l'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
l'm sorry too.
嘿  你要不要留下来
Hey, you wanna stick around
然后我帮你准备晚餐呢
and l'll whip you up some dinner?
好啊  只要是免费的
Yeah, as long as it's free.
这里的食物真的是超贵...
The food here is ridiculously overpr--
谁希望举手这件事
Who hopes the hand-raising thing
还可爱到使你不要恨我呢
is still cute enough that you won't hate me?
嘿
Hey.
乔伊  你的头后面有花生酱吗
Joey, do you have peanut butter on the back of your head?
喔  天啊  我以为我都擦掉了
Oh, man. l thought l got it all.
怎么会...
How...?
怎么弄到的呢
How?
我正在做花生酱冰沙
l was making a peanut butter smoothie, right?
我找不到果汁机
l couldn't find this little plastic thingy
上面那个小塑胶盖
that goes in the top of the blender.
然后我想
And l thought,
"那个小东西有什么重要的呢"
''Well, you know, how important can that be?'' Right?
结果是非常重要
Turns out, very.
哇  一定只是因为德雷克
Wow, definitely just Drake.
什么
What?
德雷克演得如何呢
How's it going with Drake?
我想可能演的不是很好
l don't think it's going very well.
什么
What?
我看的那一场戏很好啊
That scene l saw was so good.
我对明天要拍的那场戏
Well, l'm feeling really insecure
觉得很没安全感
about the one we're shooting tomorrow.
你是不是又故意说自己很糟
ls this that thing you do
然后让我来赞美你呢
when you say you're bad so l'll give you a compliment?
有点
A little.
不  我是真的很担心
No, l really am worried.
我必须要演得像是
l have to make it convincing
我真的爱上奥莉维亚
that l'm in love with Olivia.
所以呢
So?
所以...我从来没有演过那种戏
So l've never played that.
喔  亲爱的
Oh, honey,
那不会很难的
it can't be that hard.
你也有谈过恋爱啊
l mean, you've been in love before.
嗯  只有一次...
Well, just once...
就是跟你
...with you.
好了  这实在是有点尴尬
Okay. Well, this could be a little awkward.
我们跳过好了
l'm just gonna blow past it.
听着  你何不运用你那个特殊方法
Well, look, can't you just use that method-actor thing...
就是利用你的真实生活回忆
...where you use your real-life memories
来帮助演出呢
to help you in your performance?
你在说什么
What the hell are you talking about?
好的  只要试着回忆起
All right, look, just try to remember
你在谈恋爱时候的感觉
how you felt when you were in love...
然后在演出的时候回想起那些感觉
...and think about that when you're playing the scene.
好的  是啊  我想我做的到
Okay. Yeah, l think l can do that.
好的  有个晚会的剧情
Yeah. Okay, there's this party scene coming up.
奥莉维亚跟她老公就在那里
And Olivia and her husband are there...
而德雷克想要做的只有抓住她
...and all Drake wants to do is grab her
然后亲吻她  但是他不能
and kiss her, but he can't.
那让我想起许多时候
That makes me think about those times
我好想抓住你  然后亲吻你
l wanted to grab you and kiss you...
但是你并不知道
...but you didn't know,
所以我只能假装没事
so l would just pretend everything was cool...
但这真的让我很受折磨
...but really it was killing me.
乔伊  你从来没有说过这些
Joey, you never talked about that before.
嘿  你知道我还可以用什么吗
Hey, you know what else l could use?
有一场戏是德雷克
There's this scene
偷偷溜进奥莉维亚的房间
where Drake sneaks into Olivia's bedroom...
她不知道他就在那里
...and she doesn't know he's there,
当然  我们之间没有发生过这样的事
which never happened with us.
他知道他不应该去那里
l mean, he knows he shouldn't be there,
但是他只想看看她
but he just wants to look at her.
你知道吗
You know?
而且我记得有好那些早晨
And l remember all those mornings
就在你素颜时
before you even put on your makeup...
我也会想"天啊  她真是美丽"
...when l would think to myself, ''My God, she is beautiful.''
而且让我好心痛
And it hurt so much because l knew
因为我知道我永远不能告诉你
l could never tell you.
但是光是看着你
But it was worth it
我就觉得心满意足了
just to be there looking at you.
谢了  真是太棒了
Thanks, dude. This is great!
我从佛蒙特州帮你带了些东西
l got you something from Vermont.
卫生面条跟盐巴以外的东西吗
Besides tampons and salt?
喔  我的天
Oh, my God.
枫糖糖果  你真是贴心
Maple candy. That's so sweet of you.
真是奇怪  里面是空的
That's weird, it's empty.
嘿  你们好  干嘛呢
Hi, you guys. What's going on?
你们要一块儿呆会儿么...
You guys wanna hang out or...?
你们有听到嗡嗡声吗
Do you guys hear a buzzing?